Finding Aid for the John Thomas McGill Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Correspondence List - Outgoing
  - 2 unaddressed, 1 fragment; 1 to “Gentlemen”; 1 to “Sir”, n.d
Brundage, Albert H. (2) -- 18 Oct 1898 (to Mr. Strong); 17 Apr 1907
Bryan, W.J.S. (1) -- 20 Oct 1910
Bryant, I.H. (17) -- 22 Oct, 31 Dec 1881; 20 Jan, 1 Apr, 19 Dec 1882; 5 Feb, 26 Apr, 15 June 1883; 18 May 1884; 5 May 1885; 7 June 1889; 14, 31 Oct 1891; 14 Dec 1893; 20 Feb 1897; 4 July 1905; n.d.
Bryant, Lela Richmond (1) -- 31 Dec 1887
Buchanan, C.H. (1) -- 15 May 1901
Buffington, E.J. (1) -- 16 Dec 1908
Bull, John W. (1) -- 29 May 1913
Bulletin of Pharmacy (4) -- 26 Apr, 1 June 1910 (both to E.A. Ruddiman); 1, 21 July 1910
Buntin, Daniel C. (3) -- 29 May 1909; 6 June, 9 July 1910
Burch, Lucius (1) -- 16 May 1921
Burch, Robert L. (8) -- 22 Oct 1895; 17 May, 27 June 1905; 28 May 1907 (to Percy D. Maddin); 22 Dec 1908; 30 Jan, 1 June (to J.E. Hart) 1910; 3 Apr 1916
Burchfiel, E.G. (3) -- 12 Apr 1894; 16 Dec 1896; 1 July 1897
Burge, J.O. (2) -- 24 Feb 1893; 19 Apr 1894
Burgstahler, Herbert John (1) -- 26 Feb 1932
Burrow, C.C. (1) -- 26 Jan 1909
Burton, J.C. (1) -- 12 Apr 1912 (to G.S. Stovall)
Butler, F.E. (2) -- 18 Oct 1923; 13 Dec 1924 (to All Lovers of Poetry)
Butler, S. Goode (1) -- 25 Apr 1900
Butler, Willis P. (1) -- 27 Jun 1918
Byrne(?), Thomas S. (1) -- 21 June 1896
Cain, J.T., Jr. (3) -- 31 Jan 1915; 13 Jan, 2 Mar 1916
Caldwell, C.W. (1) -- 1 Feb 1909
Calvert, Mary R. (14) -- 4 Feb, 6 Feb 1922; 27 Feb, 17 Mar, 12 Sept, 20 Dec, 28 Dec 1923; 11 May, 20 May, 12, 18 Aug, 1 Dec 1924; 23 Nov, 13 Dec 1927
Campbell, John L. (1) -- 7 May 1891
Campbell, Lemuel R. (1) -- 22 Nov 1928
Candler, W.A. (3) -- 29 Sept, 3 Oct 1892; 2 Dec 1895
Cannon, Claude C. (5) -- 7 July, 11 Aug, 10 Sep 1910; 18 Jan 1911 (to E.A. Ruddiaan); 25 Sep 1922
Cannon, J.P. (2) -- 3, 8 Feb 1906
Carels, Joseph S. (1) -- 27 Feb 1888
Carlisle, J.C. (1) -- 1 Mar 1899
Carmichael, Emmitt B. (2) -- 27 July (to L.C. Glenn), 8 Aug 1931
Carr, Will L. (1) -- 2 Mar 1907
Carre, Henry Beach (1) -- 16 Sept 1902
Carroll, Charles G. (1) -- 14 Jun 1915
Carter, Allen R. (6) -- 11 June 1888; 13 Dec 1892; 23 Sep 1893; 17 Apr, 25 Nov 1895; 23 Jan 1909
Cartwright, R.L. (1) -- 9 Nov 1925
Casey, Mrs. (?) Lincoln (1) -- 28 Dec 1895 (to Joseph E. Washington)
Cason, Charles (2) -- 20 Oct 1914; 13 Mar 1919
Caspari, Charles, Jr. (2) -- 10 Oct 1895; 18 Oct 1917 (friends)
Cate, J. Harry (1) -- 22 Aug 1895 (to C.L. Thornburg)
Cattell, J. McK. (5) -- 21 Jan, 4 Oct (to B.R.K. Hargrove), 27 Dec 1895; 4 Aug 1900; 9 June 1903
Cawthorn, Harley (1) -- 4 Dec 1905
Central Scientific Company (1) -- 13 June 1913
Chappell, E.B. (1) -- 1 Dec 1896
Cheves, I.X. (1) -- 16 Jan 1896
Chew, R.F. (8) -- 27 Apr, 19 May, 9 Jun 1883; 10, 29 May 1884; 21 May 1885; 12 May 1887; 9 May 1889
Childress, George C. (1) -- 16 Feb 1900
Christensen, H.C. (1) -- 6 Jan 1914
Church, W.H. (1) -- 30 Apr 1916
Clack, P.D. (5) -- 14 Feb (to Editor, Christian Advocate), 1, 7 Mar, 21 Apr, 17 May 1895
Clark, Ira B. (1) -- 16 May 1913
Claxton, P.P. (3) -- 17 Jan, 9, 27 Feb 1901
Clement, W.R. (1) -- 15 Sept 1898
Cleveland, Fred A. (1) -- 11 July 1908
Clifford, George S. (1) -- 9 June 1897
Coburn, J.B. (1) -- 29 June 1910
Cody, Josh (1) -- 22 July 1924
Coffee, Maurice (1) -- 16 May 1909
Coffey, J.W. (2) -- 1 July 1898; n.d.
Cole, Fred W. (1) -- 8 June 1895 (to C.L. Thornburg)
Cole, I.H. (1) -- 22 May 1919
Cole, Whitefoord R. (2) -- 21 Oct 1895; 26 Apr 1916
Contausear(?), L. (3) -- 25 Feb 1897; 26, 27 Apr 1897 (both to M.F. Berry)
Connell, J.H. (1) -- 26 May 1909
Cook, E. Fullerton (1) -- 30 Aug 1922
Cooper, Zada M. (1) -- 22 Jan 1918
Cornick, Howard (1) -- 26 May 1916
Coston, J.T. (1) -- 12 Dec 1908
Cotton, W.H. (1) -- 12 June 1893
Craighead, E.B. (2) -- 18 Apr, 11 May 1910
Cramer, A.P. (1) -- 10 Jun 1915
Crenshaw, H.F. (1) -- 27 June 1896
Crockett, R.E. (3) -- 16, 30 May, 3 June 1893
Crockett, R.H. (1) -- 17 Dec 1892
Crockett, S.S. (3) -- 27 Apr 1895; 7 June 1897; 16 Jan 1899
Crook, A.R. (1) -- 26 Oct 1921
Cullom, M.M. (1) -- 27 May 1909 (to J.E. Hart)
Culley, M.L. (1) -- 27 Sept 1904
Cupp, Vernon (2) -- 5 July, 29 Oct 1910
Curd, Charles P. (11) -- 16, 26 Feb 1890; 1 Apr 1891; 30 Oct 1900; 19, 29 Feb, 28 Nov, 5, 6 Dec 1904; 27 Feb, 23 Mar 1905
Cushing, Daniel (3) -- 16 Jun 1901; 18 Apr, 5 Jun 1915
Dake, Walter M. (1) -- 20 Apr 1916
Dantzler, J.L. (3) -- 12 Sep 1891; 17 Apr 1893; 25 Sept 1894 (to C.L. Thornburg)
Davis, R.W. (2) -- 5 June 1894; 17 May 1895 (to C.L. Thornburg)
Davis, Samuel C. (1) -- 26 Aug 1907
Day, William B. (3) -- 12 Jan, 28 Oct 1909; 14 Feb 1911
Deering, Dorothy (1) -- n.d. (prob. 1922)
Deering, R.W. (4) -- 25 Jul 1901; 5 Nov 1902; 28 Sep 1922; 27 Dec 1927
Delgado, J.V. (5) -- 3 Jul, 1 Aug 1912; 11 May, 22 Sep 1915; 31 Oct 1917
Dement, J.J. (1) -- 31 Mar 1888
Dennis, Edward C. (2) -- 7 Sept 1893; 18 Aug 1894
Dennis, L.M. (1) -- 6 Feb 1907
Depew, Chauncey M. (1) -- 17 Dec 1892
DeWitt, John H. (1) -- 19 Feb 1909
Dickson, H.L. (1) -- 16 Apr 1918
Dictograph Products Co. (2) -- 7 Apr 1930; 6 Feb 1933
Dilly, O.C. (1) -- 27 Mar 1918 (to E.A. Ruddiman)
Dinsmore, A.W. (1) -- 13 June 1882
Dobbs, Hoyt M. (1) -- 18 Dec 1919
Dodd, T.J. (2) -- 20 Aug 1891; 26 Aug 1893
Doden, H.M.F. (1) -- 20 Mar 1918
Dodson, B.W. (1) -- 20 May 1895 (to C.L. Thornburg)
Dodson, Carl M. (2) -- 26 July 1911; 5 July 1919
Donnald, S.F. (2) -- 13 Mar 1915; 21 Apr 1918 (to E.A. Ruddiman)
Dowdy, J.F. (2) -- 28 Apr, 2 Nov 1910
Dowling, Oscar (1) -- 4 Jan 1909
Downer, J.P. (1) -- 21 July 1899
Downing, Augustus S. (1) -- 17 Jun 1912
Drug & Chemical Markets (1) -- 1 Oct 1919
Druegists Circular (7) -- 29 Apr 1901; 1 Dec 1906; 25 Jan, 14 Aug (to J.O. Schlotterbeck) 1907; 25 Apr, 11 May 1910 (both to E.A. Ruddiman; 9 Aug 1910
Dudley, William L. (15) -- 23, 29 June, 2, 29 July, 11 Aug 1887; 19 July, 6, 10, 21, 24 Aug, 27 Dec 1889; 27, 28 June, 15 July 1893; 27 Mar 1901
Duke, Charles T. (1) -- 5 June 1895 (to C.L. Thornburg)
Dunbar, C.E. (3) -- 15 July 1896; 3, 15 Sep 1897
Duncan, Chester A. (1) -- 6 Apr 1918 (to E.A. Ruddiman)
Dunn, W.A. (1) -- 16 Aug 1927
Dunn, W.W. (1) -- 15 Jan 1919
Dye, T.W. (1) -- 1 May 1899
Dye, Tom C. (1) -- 28 Oct 1898
Dyer, Arthur J. (1) -- 22 Jan 1896
Eager, Ben F., Jr. (1) -- 13 Mar 1914
Early, John (1) -- 8 June 1909 (to J.E. Hart)
Eaton, Daniel C. (1) -- 23 Apr 1884
Eberhart, Charles E. (1) -- 27 Jan 1908
Eberle, E.G. (9) -- 25 May, 15 Aug, 2, 15, Sep 1908; 7 Jun, 1 Jul 1910; 28 Aug 1913; 12 May 1914; 11 Jun 19?? (see also Southern Pharmaceutical Journal)
Eccles, R.G. (1) -- 18 Nov 1893
Edmondson, G.U. (1) -- 28 Oct 1918 (to E.A. Ruddiman)
Egelly, Alfred C. (1) -- 23 Jun 1914
Elliott, Julian (1) -- 3 July 1909
Elrod, Lawrence B. (2) -- 1, 7 Sep 1897
Emerson, W.H. (1) -- 1 May 1920
England, J.W. (3) -- 6 July 1907; 29 Aug 1908; 18 Jan 1911
Era Druggist Directory (1) -- 6 May 1898
Estes, P.M. (4) -- 16 Jul 1921; 29 Nov 1927; 2 Jun, 8 Aug 1928
Evans, T.W., Jr. (1) -- 27 May 1880
Eves, Robert L. (3) -- 26 Jan, 11 Feb, 2 Mar 1893
Ewing, Robert (2) -- 7 Jun 1915; 3 May 1916
Farnum, J.L. (3) -- 25 Apr, 16 May 1925; 10 Apr 1926
Farrell, W. Elliston (2) -- 17 May 1895 (to D.L. Thornburg); 6 June 1898
Faulkner, A.U. (4) -- 19 Nov 1896; 12 Feb, 21 May 1897; 28 Feb 1898
Faussig, F.W. (1) -- 8 Jun 1881
Featherston, L.H., Jr. (3) -- 19 Apr, 24 Jun, 21 Jul (to E.A. Ruddiman) 1918
Felts, H.D. (1) -- 19 May 1909
Ferrell, Chiles Clifton (1) -- 1 July 1895
Fite, Alexander G. (1) -- 11 Jan 1896
Fitzpatrick, J. C. (1) -- 12 May 1925
Fleming, Walter L. (2) -- 8 July 1925; 22 Sep 1927
Fleury, Frank (2) -- 9 July 1891 (to Samuel G. Butler); 25 Jul 1891
Fletcher, Duncan U. (10) -- 6 Feb 1893 (to C.L. Thornburg); 13 Jan, 14 Jun 1896; 3 Jun 1905; 25 Jan 1909; 14 Mar 1910; 5 Oct 1914; 3 Mar 1927; 10, 16 (to Mary Webb Haggard) Dec 1929
Fly, James M. (1) -- 19 Sept 1899
Ford, M.N. (1) -- 1 Jul 1918 (to E.A. Ruddiman)
Foreman, A.W. (1) -- 9 June 1908
Fort, M. Almanya (1) -- 18 June 1896
Foster, Raymond K. (1) -- 17 Feb 1920
Fox Philip (1) - 26 Nov 27
Freeman, R.W. (3) -- 29 Dec 1900; 25 Jan 1909; 20 June 1927
Frost, Edwin B. (2) -- 1 Mar 1923; 12 Dec 1927 (to J.H. Kirkland)
Fuson, H.L. (2) -- 5 Oct 1912; n.d.
Gall, George H. (1) -- 14 Apr 1916
Gallahin, J.A. (1) -- 21 Jan 1918
Gannaway, C.B. (1) -- 8 May 1903
Gannaway, Will R. (4) -- 11 Mar, 21 May 1890; 8 Mar 1901; 19 Jan 1906
Garrett, W.R. (1) -- 12 Aug 1900
Gass, Howard A. (1) -- 13, 26 Apr 1910
Gilbert, S.P. (1) -- 1 Mar 1895
Gilbett, W.H. (1) -- 25 Jun 1913
Gilmer, D.C. (1) -- 3 Dec 1895
Goodloe, Harry K. (3) -- 28 July (to E.A. Ruddiman), 4 Aug 1905; 30 Jun 1913
Goodloe, J.R. (1) -- 21 Dec 1906
Goodpasture, W.H. (1) -- 18 Nov 1895
Gordon, C.H. (1) -- 14 Dec 1930
Grainger, W.E. (12) -- 11, 19, 24, 27 June, 17, 29 July, 2, 3, 26, 31 Aug, 5 Sep, 2 Oct 1915
Grasser, John J. (1) -- 28 Jan 1918(to E.A. Ruddiman)
Gray, J.P. (1) -- 27 Jan 1908
Gray, Pleasant (2) -- 10 Sept 1893; 28 Feb 1896
Gray, Sam B. (1) -- 12 Aug 1914
Green, James B. (1) -- 28 Feb 1895
Greene, R.L. (1) -- 21 Apr 1918 (to E.A. Ruddiman)
Gregory, Willis G. (1) -- 22 Mar 1918 (to E.A. Ruddiman)
Griffin, Carlus (1) -- 1 Sep 1918(to E.A. Ruddiman)
Griffin, H.H. (1) -- 3 Jul 1897
Grigsby, John G., Jr. (1) -- 19 Dec 1905
Grossman, G.A. (1) -- 21 Mar 1918
Guerry, Alexander (1) -- 1 Apr 1930
Gurr, Minnie (1) -- 3 Jun 1918
Haack, Charlotte (1) -- 22 Dec 1907
Hadley, Arthur T. (1) -- 3 Nov 1900
Hagans, Theta(?) (2) -- 16, 28 Jun 1886
Haggard, Mary Webb (4) -- 2 Feb 1914; 12 Sep 1917 (to Asa B. Elliott); 24 May, 13 Dec 1929
Hall, Allen G. (1) -- 14 Sep 1911
Hall, Fitzgerald (2) -- 20 Apr, 3 May 1916
Hallberg, C.S.N. (3) -- 19 May 1906; 4 Dec 1907; 22 Jul 1908
Halliburton, Wesley (2) -- 18 May 1895 (to C.L. Thornburg); 10 Dec 1908 (to J.E. Hart)
Hallum, Charles M. (1) -- 16 Dec 1919
Hamner, Leon P. (1) -- 9 Jan 1918
Hamor, W.A. (1) -- 21 Aug 1922
Hardwick, George L. (1) -- 1 Aug 1889
Hardwick, J.O. (3) -- 2 Dec 1887; 20 May, 15 Jun 1891
Hargis, R.L. (1) -- 20 Apr 1918 (to E.A. Ruddiman)
Harned, Perry L. (1) -- 4 Sep 1903
Harper, William R. (1) -- 14 Dec 1895
Harrell, Ewel (1) -- 8 May 1918
Harris, James A. (3) -- 19 May 1894; 12 May 1895 (both to C.L. Thornburg); 9 June 1896
Harris, W.H. (1) -- 14 June 1893
Harrison, E.E. (2) -- 17 Jan, 9 June 1900
Harrison, J.E. (5) -- 25 June 1889; 18 June 1892; 18 Feb 1893; 4 June, 18 Sep 1923
Harrison, Joshua H. (1) -- 9 June 1894
Harrison, Thaddeus (1) -- n.d.
Harvie, Roy L. (1) -- 4 Sept 1903
Hawley, J.M. (1) -- 2 Dec 1892
Haynes, D.O. and Co. (3) -- 18 Aug, 10 Dec 1908; 1 Ju1 1910
Hays, Witherspoon (1) -- 13 Oct 1902
Hearn, E. (1) -- 15 Jul 1903
Hedgcock, George G. (1) -- 14 Aug 1915
Helmers, Otto (3) -- 13 Mar, 27 Sept 1888; 7 Jul 1889
Henderson, W.B. (1) -- 15 Jun 1898
Hendrix, E.R. (1) -- 13 May 1880
Henry, Allan J. (1) -- 12 Mar 1919
Hibbs, Henry C. (1) -- 30 Jun 1925
Hicks, G.D. (1) -- 6 Jun 1891
Hitminbotham, H.G. (1) -- 26 Mar 1919
Hill, Gretchen Lee (8) -- 5 Jul, 6 Sep 1919; 27 Jul 1931; 23 Feb, 18 Mar 1932; 5 Jan 1933; 19 Feb 1934; 17 Jun 1936
Hoag, Wenona C. (1) -- 15 Apr 1919
Hobbs, T.C. (1) -- 18 Mar 1896
Hoffman, Fred (4) -- 22 Nov, 3 Dec 1887; 6 Jan, 16 Apr 1888
Hollinshead, W.N. (2) -- 25 Jul 1887; 21 Jul 1890
Horn, P.W. (1) -- 26 Jul 1930
Hoss, E.E. (1) -- 25 Feb 1895
Houser, J.N. (1) -- 15 Nov 1915
Houston, William C. (1) -- 1 May 1917
Howard, L.O. (1) -- 7 Sep 1900
Hron, Ralph P. (1) -- 6 Jun 1914
Hughes, William (1) -- 30 Mar 1910
Hume, Alfred (4) -- 15 May 1894; 2 May 1895 (both to C.L. Thornburg); 18 Nov 1895; 10 Dec 1908
Hume, Lelan (1) - 29 May 1928 (to James I. Finney)
Humphrey, Theodore F. (1) -- 17 Mar 1899
Humphreys, Milton W. (2) -- n.d. (1909); 22 Mar 1927
Hundley, Oscar R. (1) -- 19 Dec 1908 (to J.E. Hart)
Hunnicutt, Emily (1) -- 18 Aug 1900
Hurst, Lewis M. (1) -- 26 May 1904
Jacks, M.E. (1) -- 21 Mar 1916
Jackson, C.L. (1) -- 5 Dec 1904
Jackson, Kirby E. (4) -- 21 Apr 1921; 2 Feb, 17 Sep 1925; 25 Apr 1932
James, W.J. (2) -- 3 Mar, 12 Aug 1889
Jetton, James (1) -- 24 Jul 1899
Jetton, R.L. (1) -- n.d. (frag.)
John, R.B. (1) -- 18 Apr 1885
Johnson, Dora (5) -- 29 Jan 1894 (to C.L. Thornburg); 29 Apr 1895; n.d. (3)
Johnson, Ligon (3) -- 14 Feb, 25 Mar 1916; 19 May 1917
Johnson, W. Hamilton (5) -- 16 Apr, 2 Aug (to C.L. Thornburg) 1894; n.d.; 12 Jun 1895; 5 Mar 1903
Jones, A.A. (1) -- 8 Jan 1891
Jones, E.V. (1) -- 7 Feb 1927
Jones, Elliott H. (10) -- 19, 26 May, 8 Sept 1894; 12 Apr, 3, 11, 31 May 1895; 15 Jun 1896; 10 Jun 1898; 10 Dec 1908
Jones, Ernest Victor (1) -- 14 Dec 1934
Jones, George C. (18) -- 7 May 1884; 21 Feb, 7 Mar, 2 Jun 1885; 10 Jun, 20 Aug 1888; 29 Jun 1889; 15 Mar 1892; 10 Feb, 4 Mar (2), 13 Apr, 26, 30 Sep 1893; 19 Feb, 8 Mar 1895; 22 Mar 1904; 1 Aug 1921
Jones, Grinnell (5) -- 16 Oct 1904; 5 May, 9 Oct 1905; 24 Jul 1907; 28 Apr 1916
Jones, H.E.W. (1) -- 6 June 1898
Jones, Paul M. (2) -- 28 Jun 1892 (1 to C.L. Thornburg)
Jones, R.L. (1) -- 15 Jan 1896
Jones, S.T. (1) -- 8 May 1916
Jones, Samuel J. (17) -- 9 Oct, 2 Nov, 6 Dec 1882; 3 Mar, 10 May, 5 Jun, 8 Oct, 12, 28 Nov 1883; n.d.; 25 Mar 1886; 17 Jul 1893; 6, 17 Jun 1895; 16 Jan 1896; 7, 18 Oct 1900
Joynes, Edwin S. (2) -- 14 Sep 1911; 30 Oct 1903
Kahn, Keith (1) -- 14 June 1915
Kawasaki, Chikao (24) -- 3 Sep 1903; 25, 30 Sep 190; 29 Dec 1905; 25 Dec 1911; 1 Jan 1912; 1 Jan, 25 Dec 1914; 1 Jan 1916; 1 Jan 1917; 1 Jan 1918; 1919; 1 Jan 1924; 12 Jan, 26 Dec 1925; 1 Jan 1926; 24 Dec 1929; 25 Dec 1930; 1 Jan 1932; 25 Dec 1933; n.d. (4)
Keeble, John B. (3) -- 28 May 1907 (to Percy D. Maddin); 18 Aug, 20 Nov 1918
Keeny, J. Roy (2) -- 3 Jan, 20 Mar 1915
Keesee, John W., Jr. (1) -- 2 Nov 1903
Kellar, Chambers (1) -- 4 Jan 1909 (to W.H. Witt)
Kellogg, C.S. (9) -- 22 May 1891; 10, 25 Jun, 8 Jul, 22 Oct 1895; 30 Jun 1910; 3 Sep, 2, 29 Nov 1914
Kellogg, James C. (1) -- 1 June 1910
Kelly, E.F. (1) -- 3 Apr 1918
Kelly, J.H. (1) -- 1 Nov 1891
Kercheval, Margaret (1) -- 4 May 1916
Kern, Paul B. (1) -- 3 Dec 1909
Kerr, B.B. (1) -- 21 May 1902
Kiehm, O.F. (1) -- 25 Oct 1894
King, L.M. (1) -- l8 Nov 1903 (to Dr. Hollinshead)
Kingsley, J.S. (3) -- 8 Mar, 21 Oct 1886; n.d.
Kip, H.Z. (1) -- 25 Dec 1906
Kirk, William H. (1) -- 28 Dec 1898
Kirkland, J.H. (44) -- 28 Jun, 10Jul, 20 Dec 1885; 26 Jan, 28 Feb, 17 Apr 1886; n.d.; 14, 16 Mar, 1, 6 Apr, 3, 19 Jun 1892; 9 Aug 1895; 22 Feb 1901; 26 May 1902; 7 Aug 1903; 1 Jan 1904; 19 Mar, 8 Dec 1910; 7 Jun 1911; 29 May, 13 Jun 1914; 29 Apr, 10, 14, 22.1 31 (2 - 1 to James F. Norris) May, 10 Jun 1915; 29 Feb 1916; 7 Jun 1917; 22 May, 12 Jun, 22 Sep 1919; 17 Feb 1920; 20 Mar 1924; 1 July 1925; 10 Mar, 23 Jun 1928; 8, 16 Oct 1929; 8 Jun 1933 (to W.R. Cole); n.d.
Kirkpatrick, E.T. (1) -- 1 June 1928 (to P.M. Estes)
Kirkpatrick, Walter G. (1) -- 17 Apr 1909 (to J.E. Hart)
Knapp, Bradford (1) -- 22 Mar 1928
Knox, J.W.T. (1) -- 25 Jun 1903
Koch, Julius A. (6) -- 27 Jul, 10 Dec 1909; 6, 30 Apr 1910; 20 Aug 1912; 9 Ju1 1920
Kremers, Edward (4) -- 26 Jul 1901; 10 Jan 1907; 28 Aug 1909; 7 Nov 1912
Lafferty, John J. (1) -- 12 Oct 1903
Lambourne, Lloyd (1) -- 15 May 1919
Lambuth, W.R. (1) -- 12 Feb 1909
Lamoreaux, W.F. (3) -- 3, 7, 30 Dec 1915; 10 Jan 1916
Lancaster, Emmer Martin (1) -- 25 Aug 1947
Landreth, Olin H. (3) -- 27 May 1916; 6 Dec 1927; 19 Nov 1928
Lane, Alice (1) -- 6 Aug 1890
Lane, Alvin Valentine (63) -- 10 Jun, 10 Aug 1881; 16 Jun, 5, 23 Jul, 9, 16 Sep, 20 Oct 1882; 7 Jun, 31 Jul, 20 Oct, 1 Dec 1883; 28 Jul, 4 Aug, 11 Oct, 9 Nov, 9, 21, 22 Dec 1884; 8, 17 Jan, 1 Mar, 19 Apr, 26 Jul, 16 Oct 1885; 7 Jun, 17 Jul, 2, 30 Oct, 2 Nov 1886; 5 Aug 1887; 5 Feb, 25 Mar, 26 Jul, 19 Oct 1888; 24 Jan, 15 Aug 1889; 6 May, 11 Aug 1890; 30 Mar, 10 Apr 1891; 18, 30 Jan, 6 Nov 1892; 22 Jan, 26 Mar, 5 May, 15 Aug 1893; 30 Apr, 14 Jun 1894; 15 Jan, 6 Jun 1895; 4 Mar, 11 Jun 1896; 7 Oct 1903; 16 Apr, 4 Jun, 3 Dec 1904; 4 Jan, 25 Mar, 6 Apr, 27 May 1905; 11 Dec 1908 (+ 9 programs and clippings)
Lane, Alvin Valentine, family (1) -- n.d.
Lane, J.J. (2) -- 28 Dec 1886; 8 Apr 1887
Lane, Mrs. J.J. (1) -- 17 Nov 1881
Law, W.A. (1) -- 17 Aug 1892
LaWall, Charles H. (2) -- 14 Jul 1908; n.d.
Lawrence, Charles S. (1) -- 23 Nov 1915
Lea, H.G. (5) -- 14 Jul, 2, 7, 29 Aug 1917; n.d.
Lea, J.T. (?) (1) -- 26 Aug 1918 (to E.A. Ruddiman)
Leathers, W.S. (1) -- 13 Jan 1927
Lee, Charles (1) -- 26 Mar 1918 (to E.A. Ruddiman
Lee, G.W.C. (1) -- 20 Jul 1894
Lee, Oliver J. (1) - 12 Feb 1923
Leech, Susan (1) -- 28 Sep 1903
Legate, Roy H. (1) -- 20 Apr 1911
LeGrand, M.P. (1) -- 28 Sep 1895
Leroy, Louis (12) -- 20 Feb 1901; 4 Jun, 11 Nov 1902; 20 Apr, 11 May, 6, 11, 20 Jun 1903; 8 Mar, 22 Mar, 1 Jun 1906; n.d.
Leubner, Bernhard O. (2) -- 10, 24 Apr 1902
Lewis, R.H., Jr. (1) -- 5 Jul 1910
Lide, Leslie (1) -- 30 Jul 1909
Lightfoot, Henry W. (2) -- 15 Feb, 12 Jun 1900
Lin, J. Reese (1) -- 7 Mar 1889
Linton, A.W. (1) -- 20 Feb 1909
Little, Charles E. (2) -- 30 Jun 1928; 22 Oct 1929
Loeb, Isidor (1) -- 21 Mar 1910
Loomis, H.M. (1) -- 17 Oct 1913
Looney, Mildred (1) -- 16 Dec 1933
Lopez, E.N. Bocanegra (1) -- 21 Feb 1919
Lopez, Ramon, Jr. (1) -- 10 Feb 1919 (to E.A. Ruddiman)
Lowry, John (6) -- 1, 22, 31 Dec 1881; 10 Jan, 9 Mar, 10 Apr 1882
Lupton, N.T. (1) -- 13 Mar 1893
Lutterloh, C.M. (1) -- 14 Sep 1904
Lutz, C.M. (2) -- 1 Jun 1896; 2 Apr 1920
Lyne, Roberta Dillon (21) -- 19 Aug, 20 Oct, 2, 26 Nov 1928; 15 Oct 1929; 2, 10, 16 Aug 1930; 6 Jan, 9 Feb, 11 May 1931; 8 Jun, 14 Sep 1933; 9 Jan, 6 Mar, 7 May 1934; n.d. (5) 10 posteards
Mabuy(?), C.A. (1) -- 15 May 1916
Maddin, Percy D. (15) -- 17 Jul 1906; 25 Feb, 27 May (2 - 1 to W.H. Witt, 1 to B.E. Young), 15 (to Enid Yandell), 29 (2 - 1 to Enid Yandell) June, 23 Jul (to Enid Yandell), 15 Aug. to Enid Yandell), 16 Oct. (to Enid Yandell) Aug, 28 Oct 1907; 8 Jan 1908; 2 Mar, 7 May (to J.E. Hart) 1910
Maddin, Thomas L. (1) -- 12 Mar 1890
Magruder, William T. (1) -- 21 Apr 1916
Maher, James D. (23) -- 11, 22 Jun, 2, 31 Jul, 1, 5 Aug, 14, 24 Sep, 5, 9 Oct, 3, 22, 29 Nov 1915; 3, 5 (2), 18 Jan, 1, 5, 15 Apr, 11, 12, 16 May 1916
Mahoney, J.O. (1) -- 2 Jul 1896
Major, B.C. (1) -- 10 Mar 1919
Malloy, V.D. (1) -- 23 Aug 1909
Manlove, A.G. (1) -- 19 Feb 1900
Manning, Van H. (1) -- 18 Jan 1916
Maurice, Will H. (4) -- 28 May 1907 (to Percy D. Maddin); 10 Dec 1908 (to J.E. Hart); 7, 11 Jun 1909
Marmaduke, J.M. (1) -- 22 Jan 1896
Marr, Goulding (1) -- 11 Dec 1908
Marr, Robert H. (4) -- 4 Mar, 9 Dec 1895; 18 May, 7 Jun 1905
Marshall and Bruce Co. (1) -- 31 May 19o4
Martin, Charles S. (1) -- 26 Aug 1907
Martin, George W. (2) -- 11, 25 Jun 1900
Martin, W.H. (1) -- 22 Aug 1918
Mason, Harry B. (7) -- 6 Aug 1904; 29 May, 5 Jun, 21, 29 Aug 1905; 28 Dec 1911; 1 Ju1 1915
Massey, F.M. (1) -- 1 Sep 1909
Massey, Noble C. (1) -- 17 Jul 1919
Mayfield, G.R. (1) -- 10 Jul 1905
McAllester, Sam J. (2) -- 10, 12 Apr 1916
McClanahan, Charles (1) -- 18 Jan 1919
McClure, James M. (3) -- 1 Jul 1895 (to C.L. Thornburg); 10 July 1896 (to W.H. Hollinshead); 27 Sep 1897
McConnell, C.C. (1) -- 12 Oct 1920
McCorkle, J.W. (4) -- 22 Jun, 2 Jul, 23 Nov 1900; n.d. (frag.)
McCorkle, Norman (1) -- 6 Sep 1900
McDavid, David A. (1) -- 11 Sep 1907
McDougal, John D. (1) -- 30 Mar 1903
McDougal, W.E. (1) -- 17 Sept 1905
McGehee, Nat (1) -- 5 May 1915
McGhee, J.L. (5) -- 1 Mar 1905; 3 May 1919; 24 Oct 1921; 10, 23 Jul 1924
McGill, John M. (4) -- 4, 12 Jun, 3, 11 Jul 1906
McIlhenny, John A. (2) -- 5 Jun 1917; Jul 1917
McIntyre, Robert (1) -- 15 Dec 1908
McKee, Mrs. A.E. (1) -- n.d.
McKnight, H.M. (2) -- 18 Feb, 14 Mar 1896
McMullen, J.P. (5) -- 30 Dec 1897; 15, 21 Feb, 2, 10 May 1898
McReynolds, J.C. (1) -- n.d.
McTyeire, Holland N. (3) -- 29 Mar, 21 Apr, 21 Jun 1886
McTyeire, Holland N., Jr. (1) -- 15 Jul 1882
Meixell, Granville H. (1) -- 25 May 1895
Menees, ---- (1) -- 25 Feb 1896
Menke, A.E. (1) -- 20 Oct 1894
Merck’s Market Report (1) -- 23 Jul 1892
Meriwether, Hunter M. (4) -- 16 Feb (to C.L. Thornburg 1892; 15 June 1893 (to C.L. Thornburg); 23 May 1894 (to C.L. Thornburg); 12 June 1896
Merriam, Thomas N. (2) -- 12 Sept 1894 (to C.L. Thornburg); 29 May 1895
Merrick, Edwin (5) -- 12 (2 - 1 to J.E. Hart), 19 Dec 1908; 6 May 1916; 22 Feb 1927
Merrill, George P. (2) -- 19 Apr, 4 May 1927
Meyer Brothers Druggist (8) -- 17 Feb, 21 Apr 1896; 25 May 1899; 2 Jan, 20 Oct 1906; 10 Apr, 26 Sep, 9 Oct 1907 (see also Whelpley)
Midland Publishing Company (2) -- 15, 29 Mar 1909
Miller, E.H. (4) -- 20, 21 (to J.H. Kirklnnd), 28 Aug 1918; n.d. (to E.A. Ruddiman)
Miller, W.B. (14) -- 17 (2 - 1 to Clifford Walker), 19 (to Clifford Walker) Nov, 24 Dec 1915; 4, 8, 11, 25 Jan, 3 (3), 22, 24(to James D. Maher), 27 Mar 1916
Mills, D.I. (2) -- 11, 24 May 1901
Mills, Horace A. (1) -- 21 Aug 1917
Mims, Edwin (1) -- 20 May 1895 (to C.L. Thornburg)
Mitchell, Charles S. (1) -- 1 Jul 1929
Mitchell, S.A. (1) - 10 Dec 1927
Moffatt, C.L. (2) -- 21 Feb, 25 Jun 1908
Moon, H.C. (2) -- 16, 27 feb 1900
Moore, R.G. (1) -- 21 Jan 1909
Moore, Frederick W. (1) -- 15 May 1909
Moore, Maude (1) -- 21 Oct 1904
Moore, W.V. (1) -- 31 Jan 1896
Moore, William L. (1) -- 9 Oct 1900
Moose, L. (1) -- 23 Jan 1909
Morehouse, D.W. (2) -- 6 Apr, 14 May 1930
Morgan, Henry W., Jr. (7) -- 3 Mar 1890; 15, 20 Jul, 14 Oct 1895; 9 Jan, 13 Jun 1896; 17 Mar 1911
Morgan, William H. (1) - 12 Apr 1928
Morrell, Norman B. (4) -- 29 Mar, 16, 22, 23 May 1916
Moseley, C.B. (2) -- 10 Jun, 7 Oct 1895
Murphy, Elmer G. (1) -- 17 May 1919
Nance, W.B. (2) -- 2 Ju1 1915; 13 Jul 1931
National Association of Drug Clerks (3) -- 2, 12 Oct, 10 Nov 1916
National Pharmaceutica1 Agency (1) -- 27 Mar 1905
Neilson, Douglas (2) -- 5 Jul, 1 Sep 1897
Neilson, P.D. (2) -- 18 Sep, 11 Oct 1897
Nelson, Wilbur A. (2) -- 11, 14 Ju1 1921
Newman, Floyd (1) -- 22 Jul 1918
Newton, Howard C. (1) -- 18 Jan 1918
Nichols, J.W. (1) -- 23 Apr 1894
Niohols, Mrs. M.F. (1) -- 13 Mar 1905 (to M.E. Holderness)
Nish, F.W. (1) -- 25 Mar 1919 (to E.A. Ruddiman)
Nixon, C.F. (1) -- 1 Apr 1920
Norris, E.L. (1) -- 8 Feb 1918
Norton, Thomas H. (1) -- 26 Apr 1916
Nunn, Roscoe (4) -- 7 Feb, 19, 20 Apr 1922; 10 Mar 1923
O’Callaghan, W.J. (1) -- 27 Jun 1927
O’Connor, Andrew (1) -- 31 Dec 1895
O’Connor, Myles P. (3) -- 26 (2 - 1 to Frank Wade), 29 Aug 1912
Odell, Allan F. (7) -- 30 June (to M.E. Holderness), 4 Jul 1904; 21 Mar 1908; 1, 27 Jul, 11 Aug 1909; n.d. (frag.)
Oden, L.H. (1) -- 8 Oct 1927
Oesterling, H. Carl (1) -- 30 Dec 1930
O’Gara, P.J. (1) -- 11 May 1916
Oglesby, K.G. (2) -- 14 Jul 1910
Oglesby, R.M. (1) -- 27 Jan 1911
Ogrer, W.R. (1) -- 7 Nov 1905
O’Knott (?), John (2) - 8 Aug, 24 Aug 1944
Oldberg, Oscar (17) -- 11, 31 Oct 1894; 26 Aug, 24 Sep 1895; 12 Oct 1905; 17, 25 (?) May, 4, 11 Jun, 5 Jul, 4 Aug (2 - 1 to J.W. England) 1906; 12 Jan, 11 Sep, 8 Oct 1907; 7 Jan 1908
Orme, James H. (1) -- 20 Jan 1909
Overbury, John T. (1) -- 3 Dec 1915
Overstreet, J.B. (3) -- 18 Aug, 20 Sep 1915; 7 Jan 1916
Palmer, Howard E. (5) -- 14, 15 Sep, 3, 17, 26 Oct 1915
Palmer, W.B. (1) -- 22 Apr 1894
Palmore, W.B. (4) -- 29 Nov 1892 (2); 26 Feb, 17 Jul 1895
Parke, Hank, Jr. (1) -- 16 Jun 1891 (to Ed ----)
Parke, Davis & Co. (8) -- 1 Nov 1890; 2 Jul 1901; 7 Apr 1904; 18 Apr 1905; 3 May 1906; 17 Apr 1907; 27 Apr 1911; 6 May 1914
Parker, Chester (3) -- 22 Jan, 12 Feb 1917; 18 Dec 1918 (to Mr. Hamilton)
Parkhurst, J.A. (1) - 10 Feb 1923
Parsons, Charles L. (2) -- 17 May 1921; 19 Nov 1935
Paschall, Freeman F. (1) -- 18 Jan 1906
Payne, Bruce R. (1) -- 6 Jun 1929
Peirce, George J. (1) -- 3 Jul 1916
Pemberton, Myrtle (1) -- 31 Jan 1918
Perusse, Francis J. (3) -- 21 Nov 1917; 26, 31 Jan 1918 (all to E.A. Ruddiman)
Petit, A. (1) -- 11 Ju1 1907
Picton, John M. (1) -- 4 Feb 1896
Pipkin, E.M. (2) -- 18 Feb 1896; 5 Aug 1901
Plautz, S. (1) -- 31 Aug 1907
Polk, Prudeuce (2) - 23, 30 May 1928
Porter, Philip H. (4) -- 6 Feb 1893; 20 Apr, 22 May 1894; 6 June 1895 (all to C.L. Thornburg)
Powell, Lewis (1) -- 6 Dec 1900
Pratt, N.P., Laboratory (3) -- 28 Jun, 15, 21 Ju1 1915
Praxedes, Nother Superior (2) -- 21 May, 8 Jun 1900
Price, George H. (2) -- 9 Oct 1895; n.d.
Proctor, Richard A. (1) -- 24 Mar 1880 (autograph only)